

aboutMe.js





20 years-old

LANGUAGES

pt_BR = Native
en_US = Fluent
LIBRAS = Basic

SKILLS

JavaScript •••• ReactJS NodeJS Bootstrap ••• CSS in JS APIs Git C / C++ Office



github.com/brinobruno



linkedin.com/in/brunociao



brunosantos6ft@gmail.com



+55 12 98898 1915



São José dos Campos, São Paulo - Brazil

const myName = 'Bruno Corrêa'

let myOccupation = 'Frontend Developer'

A true knowledge lover, I believe in the power of technology and education to change lives. Working with Web Development with emphasis on Frontend since 2020. Always concerned with the user experience alongside metrics and data for high-retention rates.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Jun 2021 - Currently { Remote - Brazil)
TechPark - Kukka Educação
Internship = Software Developer

As an intern in one of the TechPark's most prosperous startups, I'm building inovative learning platforms using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP and Wordpress. These projects will impact thousands of students.



Aug 2020 - Apr 2021 { São José dos Campos, Brazil }
Inglês Smart
Graphic Designer

I lead UI/UX projects with Figma and Adobe XD on the school's platforms, as well as the design of the visual identity, audiovisual productions and teaching materials with Illustrator, Photoshop and Premiere Pro.

MAIN PERSONAL PROJECTS

```
Jun 2021 - Sep 2021 { link: meuport.com }
MeuPort - JavaScript, Jquery, CSS, PHP, Git
```

Nov 2021 - { link: https://main.d1umw160g6fy01.amplifyapp.com/ }
React todo - JavaScript, Typescript, AWS, Git

ACADEMIC EDUCATION



Higher Education { Jacareí - Brazil }
Development and Analysis of Systems
3º semester

VOLUNTEER WORK

```
Apr 2020 - Jul 2020 { Remote - Brazil }
IFSP - English Teacher
```